<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
	<!-- Mod Settings -->
	<D9FSettingsCategory>D9 Framework</D9FSettingsCategory>
	<D9FSettingsDebug>Debug</D9FSettingsDebug>
	<D9FSettingsDebugTooltip>Enable debug logging, especially on load. You generally don't need to enable this unless asked to.</D9FSettingsDebugTooltip>
	<D9FSettingsPPM>Print patched methods</D9FSettingsPPM>
	<D9FSettingsPPMTooltip>Whether to print all the Harmony patches which are successfully applied.</D9FSettingsPPMTooltip>
	<D9FSettingsApplyAtOwnRisk>Disabling any patches may result in unpredictable behavior and features breaking. Only disable them if you know what you're doing!</D9FSettingsApplyAtOwnRisk>
	<D9FSettingsDebugModeRequired>If debug mode is disabled, all patches will be applied.</D9FSettingsDebugModeRequired>
	<D9FSettingsRestartToApply>You must restart the game for patch settings to apply.</D9FSettingsRestartToApply>
	<D9FSettingsApplyCFS>Apply CompFromStuff patch</D9FSettingsApplyCFS>
	<D9FSettingsApplyCFSTooltip>Whether to apply the CompFromStuff patch, which allows materials to add additional properties to things made therefrom.</D9FSettingsApplyCFSTooltip>
	<D9FSettingsApplyOTH>Apply Orbital Trade Hook patch</D9FSettingsApplyOTH>
	<D9FSettingsApplyOTHTooltip>Whether to apply the Orbital Trade Hook patch, which allows modders to create custom trade beacons.</D9FSettingsApplyOTHTooltip>
	<D9FSettingsApplyDRF>Apply Deconstruct Return Fix patch</D9FSettingsApplyDRF>
	<D9FSettingsApplyDRFTooltip>Whether to apply the Deconstruct Return Fix patch, which fixes a vanilla bug which prevents buildings from returning all their items when deconstructed.</D9FSettingsApplyDRFTooltip>
	<D9FSettingsApplyCMF>Apply Carry Mass Framework patches</D9FSettingsApplyCMF>
	<D9FSettingsApplyCMFTooltip>Whether to apply the patches for the Carry Mass Framework, which allows mod authors to modify the way carry mass works in game.</D9FSettingsApplyCMFTooltip>
	<D9FSettingsApplyNFP>Apply Negative Fertility Patch</D9FSettingsApplyNFP>
	<D9FSettingsApplyNFPTooltip>Whether to apply the Negative Fertility Patch, which allows specific plants to grow faster in less fertile soil.</D9FSettingsApplyNFPTooltip>
	<D9FSettingsApplyFRF>Apply Facility Requires Fuel patch</D9FSettingsApplyFRF>
	<D9FSettingsApplyFRFTooltip>Whether to apply the Facility Requires Fuel patch, which allows modders to create facilities which require fuel to operate.</D9FSettingsApplyFRFTooltip>
	<D9FSettingsApplyCBR>Apply Calculate Bleed Rate patch</D9FSettingsApplyCBR>
	<D9FSettingsApplyCBRTooltip>Whether to apply the Calculate Bleed Rate patch, which allows modders to apply bleed rate modifiers on pawns using a stat.</D9FSettingsApplyCBRTooltip>
	<D9FSettingsApplyHRP>Apply Healing Rate Patch</D9FSettingsApplyHRP>
	<D9FSettingsApplyHRPTooltip>Whether to apply the Healing Rate Patch, which allows modders to apply healing rate modifiers on pawns using a stat.</D9FSettingsApplyHRPTooltip>
	<!-- AJO PlaceWorkers -->
	<D9F_Roofed_NeedsRoof>{0} needs to be placed under a roof</D9F_Roofed_NeedsRoof>
	<D9F_Chandelier_TooTall>{0} is too tall to place a {1} here</D9F_Chandelier_TooTall>
	<D9F_MustBePlacedOnWall>{0} must be placed on a wall</D9F_MustBePlacedOnWall>	
	<!-- IngredientValueGetter_Mass -->
	<D9F_BillRequiresMass>Requires {0}kg of {1}</D9F_BillRequiresMass>
</LanguageData>